[
    {
        "title": "Color Quiz"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What color is the gemstone sapphire?",
        "answer": "Blue."
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What color is often associated with envy?",
        "answer": "Green."
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What color is created by combining all the colors of light?",
        "answer": "White."
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What color is the blood of an octopus?",
        "answer": "Blue."
    },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What color is the primary pigment used in traditional Chinese ink?",
        "answer": "Black."
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What color is the traditional uniform of the British royal guards?",
        "answer": "Red."
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "In the flag of Italy, which color is positioned on the left?",
        "answer": "Green."
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which color is often associated with the team kits of the Italian national football team?",
        "answer": "Blue."
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is the surname of the character played by Bryan Cranston in Breaking Bad?",
        "answer": "White."
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What colour is the outer rim of the Nepalese Flag?",
        "answer": "Blue."
    }
]
